SHREYA HEGDE

8105978828 • shreyahegde93@gmail.com • Bangalore

SUMMARY

Over 7+ years of experience in the IT industry as a Front-End Developer(React JS) with web-based applications. Aspiring to pursue a challenging career in the Information Technology industry that explores my ingenuity resourcefulness and potential to the fullest and contribute to the company's growth.

SKILLS

React JS, Material UI, Formik, Hooks, Axios Calls, HTML, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, LESS, Bootstrap 4, JSON, JavaScript ES6, i18, Redux, React Native, WordPress, Postman, Swagger, Git repository, Scrum Master, Adobe Photoshop & Adobe XD.0

EXPERIENCE

ZKTECO Biometric R&D, Bangalore

Oct 2020 - Present

Senior Software Engineer

- Developed internal web applications using ReactJS, Hooks, Material UI, Redux, reusable components, and routing to implement navigation between the components.
- Implemented internationalization using React, Hooks, and il8n, resulting in an increase in adoption rates across the web application.
- · Worked across different browsers and devices. Debug and fix compatibility issues.
- Collaborating with Product Team, UX team, and backend developers to useable and innovative interfaces to serve our customers and also fix bugs after deployment to staging before it goes to production.

Resolve Biz Apps & Services, Bangalore

May 2018 - Oct 2020

Front End Web Developer

- Designed and developed a responsive website for an NGO using Bootstrap, Javascript, and HTML5, and an E-Commerce website using WordPress ensuring modern interface design.
- Established front-end web application structure and UI layout using React JS, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and Email Template.
- Worked on Agile methodologies for code evolution, and Strong Experience in GIT, Control Version & Source Code Management.

Socioactiv Brand Solutions, Bangalore

May 2017 - May 2018

Web Developer

- Developed e-commerce responsive web application using HTML5, Javascript, HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap.
- Design, Develop, and implement a responsive web application that works across all browsers & mobile devices.

INTERNSHIP

Advanced Diploma in Software Programming - RiiiT Finishing School Mysore

2016 - 2017

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science

2011 - 2015

SDM Institute of Technology Ujire, Mangalore, Karnataka